CHRISTOPHER R. JORDAN

Denver, CO | (C) 303-726-2125 | CRobertJordan1991@yahoo.com

Professional Summary

I'm a creative front-end developer who enjoys designing and developing UI/UX web experiences with a focus on usability and accessibility standards. My passion for software development pushes me to learn and refine my skills through a variety of means. I enjoy working on complex problems, learning from peers and mentors, and I strive to bring positive energy to every project I'm a part of.

Skills

HTML5 Unit Testing

CSS3/Sass Frameworks Version Control
Javascript (ES6) Browser Development Tools

jQuery Ember
Responsive Web Design Express
React/React Native Node
Redux SEO

Education

Web Development: Front End Engineering

2017

Turing School of Software and Design - Denver, CO

An intensive seven-month program focusing on HTML, CSS, Web Development with JavaScript,
 Professional Client-Side Development, Desktop and Mobile Applications with Web Technologies.

Bachelor of Arts: History

August 2010

Metropolitan State University of Denver - Denver, Colorado

- Outstanding Achievement Award
- Bachelor of Arts in History · Entered August 2010 · Graduate Class of Spring 2016

Work History

Telecommunications Technician

06/2016 to 01/2017

TAK Communication - Denver, CO

• Maintained, constructed, and repaired infrastructure and equipment used for Comcast services.

Substitute Teacher and Teacher Aid

01/2016 to 06/2016

Rantoul School District - Rantoul, Illinois

Successfully facilitated a variety of subjects in elementary and middle school classrooms.

Data Collector/Field Researcher

07/2015 to 12/2015

ETC Institute - Denver, Colorado

 Developed qualitative and quantitative customer satisfaction research for state and local governments. Worked closely with business owners and managers to collect viable data which was utilized by the Colorado Department of Transportation to coordinate the traffic and road construction of major areas in Colorado.

English Teacher 02/2015 to 06/2015

Learn English - Chengdu, China

 Conducted English lessons on a one-on-one setting for Chinese students and young professionals, ranging from basic to advanced levels of proficiency.

Phone Receptionist 01/2014 to 10/2014

Auraria Health Center - Denver, Colorado

Customer Service/Office Clerk position with the responsibility of assisting patients with scheduling
appointments, coordinating individuals to proper channels, and other phone inquiries. Also fulfilled
data entry and conducted general office tasks.

Cook/Cashier 01/2013 to 08/2013

LarkBurger - Denver, Colorado

 Prepared food from raw goods to final product, maintain the kitchen and front of house, customer service, and handling of customer transactions for a thriving, young franchise out of Colorado.

Secretary 01/2010 to 02/2013

R.V Consulting - Denver, Colorado

Customer Service position committed to administrative and assisting with general office tasks.

References

